{
  "easy": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "This is question 1",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "c"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "This is question 2",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "This is question 3",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "d"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "This is question 4",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "b"
    }
  ],
  "medium": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "This is question 1 medium",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "c"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "This is question 2 medium",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "This is question 3 medium",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "This is question 4 medium",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "b"
    }
  ],
  "difficult": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "This is question 1 difficult",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "This is question 2 difficult",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "This is question 3 difficult",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "This is question 4 difficult",
      "responses": {
        "a:": "Option a",
        "b:": "Option b",
        "c": "Option c",
        "d": "Option d"
      },
      "correct": "a"
    }
  ]
}
